Finding Aid for the W.W. Robinson papers, ca. 1843-1972
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Research material: Abstracts of title - city, rancho properties.
  - Abstract of the title to all that certain tract of land situated in Los Angeles County, State of California borrowed and described as follows tomb. That certain part of the portion of the Cienega Rancho., 1885; 1 v. (Box 71, Folder 2)
    La Cienega - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Los Angeles Abstract Company.
  - Abstract of title covering portion of Rancho covering La Cienegas That part of the first tract of the Jauwario Abila tract in the Rancho La Cienega., 1888; 1 v. Bound in green leather with gold stamping. (Box 71, Folder 3)
    La Cienega - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - Abstract of title of all that real property tat situate in the City of and County of Los Angeles of the boundary line survey of the rancho Ex Mission de San Fernando., 1928; 1 v. Blue cover with gold lettering. (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Mission San Fernando - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Title Guarantee and Trust Co.
  - Abstract of title to all that certain tract of real propertycommencing at the intersection of the West line of the South east Quarter of the North West Quarter of Section 11 and the north line of San Gabriel Orange Grove Tract., ca. 1907; 1 v. In wrappers. (Box 71, Folder 5)
    Mission San Gabriel - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the County of Los Angeles, State of California, bounded and described as follows: Rancho Potrero de Felipe Lugo., 1912; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Potrero de Felipe Lugo - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - Felipe Lugo Rancho Report of James L. Robinson on certain defects and outstanding interests affecting the title of the estate of E.J. Baldwin to that portion of the Rancho now owned or claimed by the estate., 1912; 1 v. Leather bound. (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Transcript of the proceedings in case no. 433The petition of George Morrillo and Maria V. Romero for the place named Potrero De Felipe Lugo., ca. 1887; 1 v. In wrappers. (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the County of Los Angeles, State of California, bounded and described as follows: Rancho Providencia, Rancho Cahuenga and that portion of the Rancho San Rafael., ca. 1892.; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Providencia - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the County of Los Angeles, State of California, bounded and described as follows: the Rancho Rincon de Los Bueyes., 1892; 1 v. In marble boards. (Box 72, Folder 4)
    Rincon de los Bueyes - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the Rancho San Antonio county of Los Angeles State of California bounded and described as follows: the Felipe Lugo Tract., 1879; 1 v. In cloth boards. (Box 72, Folder 5)
    San Antonio (Lugo) - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - Abstract of title to that real property situate in the County of Los Angeles, State of California, described as follows: Rancho La Laguna., 1874; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 72, Folder 6)
    San Antonio (Rancho la Laguna) - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Title Insurance and Trust Company.
  - Abstract of title to that portion of the Rancho Rodeo de Los Aguas or San Antonio., 1871; 1 v. In marble boards. (Box 72, Folder 7)
    San Antonio or Rodeo de las Aguas - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the Rancho San Francisquito County., 1894; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 72, Folder 8)
    San Francisquito - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Title Insurance and Trust Company.
  - [Rancho San Pasqual]., 1873; 1 v. Bound in full red leather. (Box 73, Folder 1)
    San Pasqual - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the Rancho San Pasqual., 1886; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Abstract of title of the following property situate in the County of Los Angeles, State of California particularly described as follows, to wit: Being lots number two and five in Block A of the Rancho San Pedro., 1884; 1 v. In paper boards. (Box 73, Folder 3)
    San Pedro - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Galloway and Lienau.
  - Patent to Rancho San Pedro., ca. 1892; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 73, Folder 4)
    San Pedro (Inner Bay, Rattlesnake Island, Salt Flats) - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Los Angeles Terminal R'y Co.
  - Report and opinion on title of Ana Josefa Dominguez de Guyerto those portions of the Rancho San Pedro, situated in the county of Los Angeles, State of California, known as "Rattlesnake Island",., 1891; 1 v. In black cloth. (Box 73, Folder 5)
    San Pedro (Inner Bay, Rattlesnake Island, Salt Flats) - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Lee and Scott.
  - Abstract of title and certificate of search to all of that certain tract of land situate in the County of Los Angeles, State of California, described as follows: at a point on the exterior boundary of the Rancho San Pedro., ca. 1892; V. 1. Bound in half leather. (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Abstract of title to that real property., ca. 1892; V. 2. Bound in half leather. (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - [Taxes and wharf franchise]., ca. 1892; V. 5. Bound in half leather. (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - [Index]., ca. 1892; Bound in half leather. (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the County of Los Angeles, State of California, bounded and described as follows: The interest of Ralph Rogers in the Garavanza lands., 1887; 1 v. In wrappers. (Box 75, Folder 1)
    San Rafael - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - [Rancho San Rafael]., 1893; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 75, Folder 2)
    San Rafael (Verdugo Ranch) - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - The Abstract Title Insurance Co.
  - San Vincente y Santa Monica, Boca de Santa Monica, Potrero de Santa Monica as to the interest acquired by Robert S. Baker and John P. Jones., 1933?; 1 v. In wrappers. (Box 75, Folder 3)
    San Vincente y Santa Monica - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - Abstract of title --- that portion of the Rancho Santa Anita which lies within the boundaries of the tract described on page 169 hereof and also within the boundaries., 1892?; 1 v. Bound in half leather (damaged). (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Santa Anita - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - The Abstract Title Insurance Co. of Los Angeles, Cal.
  - Abstract of title of thatportion of the Rancho Santa Anita., 1892; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Santa Anita - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - The Abstract and Title Insurance Co.
  - Abstract of title to that certain real property situate in the county of Los Angeles, State of California and known as the island of Santa Catalina., 1891; 1 v. In marble boards. (Box 75, Folder 5)
    Santa Catalina Island - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - Abstract of title to that real property situated in the County of Los Angelesknown as the J.W. Hellman Tract of the Colima Tract of the Santa Gertrude., 1893; 1 v. Bound in leather. (Box 75, Folder 6)
    Santa Gertrudes - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Los Angeles Abstract Co.
  - Index to Simi Rancho., ca. 1919?; 1 v. In wrappers (cover missing). (Box 75, Folder 7)
    Simi - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - [Rancho Simi]., CHECK DATE; 1 v. In wrappers. (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Los Angeles, State of California, bounded and described as follows: Rancho Tajauta or Los Cuervos., 1892; 1 v. (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Tajauta - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the County of.
  - Office abstract of Rancho Tajauta or Los Cuervos., ca. 1874; 1 v. In marble boards, cloth spine. (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Tajauta - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - [Probate court].
  - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the Rancho Tujunga., 1892; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Tujunga - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - [Rancho Del Paso]., 1910; 1 v. In wrappers. (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Del Paso - Ranchos, Sacramento County - Buckley - Gerber Abstract and Title Co.
  - Abstract of title of the following described properly, situate in the County of San Bernardino, State of California., 1893; V. 1 of 2. Bound in half leather. (Box 76, Folder 4)
    Muscupiabe - Ranchos, San Bernardino County - [No compiler given].
  - [Muscupiabe]., 1893; V. 2 of 2. Bound in half leather. (Box 76, Folder 5)
    Muscupiabe - Ranchos, San Bernardino County - Consolidated Abstract and Title Guaranty Co.
  - Abstract of title to all that certain real property situate, lying and being in the County of Santa Barbaraa part of the Rancho Dos Pueblos., 1923; 1 v. (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Dos Pueblos - Ranchos, Santa Barbara County - Santa Barbara Abstract and Guaranty Company Co.
  - Abstract of title to San Julian Rancho, vol. 4., 1894; 1 v. Map of the Rancho. (Box 77, Folder 2)
    San Julian - Ranchos, Santa Barbara County - [No compiler given].
  - Abstract of title to all that certain real property situated in the County of Santa Barbarabeing the Rancho San Julian, part of Rancho Las Cruces, Co., showing their division into tracts A, B C., 1907; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 77, Folder 3)
    San Julian - Ranchos, Santa Barbara County - Santa Barbara Abstract and Title Co.
  - Abstract of title as to the interest of the heirs of Francisco Antonio de la Guerrain and to the Rancho De Las Posas., 1919; 1 v. In wrappers. (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Las Posas - Ranchos, Ventura County - [No compiler given].
  - Abstract of title to that real property situated in the County of Los Angelesalloted to Inez Ramirez de Pantoja., 1891; 1 v. Bound in leather. (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Ramirez Vineyard - County Properties, Los Angeles County - Los Angeles Abstract Co.
  - [Southern Pacific right of way]., 1930; 1 v. (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Southern Pacific - County Properties, Los Angeles County - Title Insurance and Trust Co.
  - The United States of America gives and grants unto the confirmee in coordination of the full payment for the same having been made, the following described lands situate in San Bernardino County., No date; 1 v. (Box 78, Folder 4)
    Township 3 - County Properties, San Bernardino County - Wozencraft Abstract Co.
  - Abstract of title to that certain real property in the leity of Los Angeles Countyat the N.W. corner of the 16 acre lot of A.L. Moody sold to him by William Moody and running along his west line south 39.1 chains to the Ballona Road., 1887; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Ballona Road - City Properties, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - Abstract of title to certain property in Los Angeles City, California belonging to Mrs. Arcadia B. de Baker as delineated on the map hereto annexed., 1884; 1 v. (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Bandini de Baker Property - City Properties, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - Abstract of title to all that certain real property situated in the City of Los Angeles and county of Los Angelessaid tract of land being known as the Cota Lot or tract., 1888; 1 v. (Box 79, Folder 3)
    Cota Tract - City Properties, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the County of Los Angelesthe Downey Tract., 1884; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 79, Folder 4)
    Downey Tract - City Properties, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the City of Los Angeleslot 16, block 9, Fairmont Tract., 1889; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 79, Folder 5)
    Fairmont Tract - City Properties, Los Angeles County - Abstract and Title Insurance Co.
  - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the City of Los Angeles, State of California, bounded and described of page no. 61 of this abstractbeing Lot no. 11 in Block no. 4 of East Los Angeles., 1890; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 79, Folder 6)
    Hayes Street, East Los Angeles - City Properties, Los Angeles County - Los Angeles Abstract Co.
  - [Property of Mary E. Taft]., 1894; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 79, Folder 7)
    Hill and Fifth Street, Northwest Corner - City Properties, Los Angeles County - Los Angeles Abstract Co -
  - Continuation by the Title Insurance and Trust Company as to Larronde Block, N.W. corner of Spring and First Streets., 1899; V. 1. Bound in half leather. (Box 79, Folder 8)
    Larronde Block - City Properties, Los Angeles County - Title Insurance and Trust Co - N. W. corner of Spring and First Streets
  - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the City and County of Los Angelescommencing at the point of intersection of the Westerly boundary line of the City of Los Angeles., 1888; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 80, Folder 1)
    Los Angeles Westerly Boundary - City Properties, Los Angeles County - Abstract and Title Insurance Co.
  - Abstract of title to that real property situate in the City and County of Los Angelesfronting eighty-five feet on Main Street, as described in deed from D.W. Hellman to Samuel Meyer., 1895; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 80, Folder 2)
    Main Street, 85 Feet Near 4th Street - City Properties, Los Angeles County - Title Insurance and Trust Co.
  - Abstract of title to that real property in the City and County of Los Angeles, State of California, described as follows, to-wit: lot seven block O. Mott tract., 1889; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    Mott Tract - City Properties, Los Angeles County - Pendleton and Williams.
  - Abstract of title to five acres of James F. Ward on Pearl St. in Los Angeles City and County., 1887; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    Pearl Street - City Properties, Los Angeles County - No title.
  - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the City of Los Angeles County of Los Angeles, State of California, bounded and described as follows: The Pico House property., 1883; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    Pico House Property - City Properties, Los Angeles County - Office of Gillette, Gibson, and Wood.
  - The Security Title Insurance and Abstract Co. of Southern California hereby certifiesa point in the West line of Euclid Avenue distant sixty six feet N of the S line of Lot no. 3 in Block 1 of the San Pascual Tract., 1892; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 80, Folder 6)
    San Pascual Tract - City Properties, Los Angeles County - Lot 3 Block 1
  - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the City of Los Angelescommencing in the easterly line of Spring St., 1899; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 80, Folder 7)
    Spring Street, East Side Near 1st Street - City Properties, Los Angeles County - Title Insurance and Trust Co.
  - Abstract of title to that real property situated in the county of Los Angelesbeginning at the North West corner of Spring and First Streetsbeing the lot of Pierre Larronde., 1892; 1 v. Bound in leather. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    Spring and First Street, Corner - City Properties, Los Angeles County - Los Angeles Abstract Co.
  - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the City and County of Los Angelescommencing at a point in the south line of Washington Street at the N.W. corner of this tract of landcontaining 563 acres., 1890; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    Washington Street, Near San Pedro - City Properties, Los Angeles County - [No compiler given].
  - Abstract of title of Lots 25 and 26 of the Wright Tract, northeast corner of Washington and Figueroa Streets., 1888; 1 v. In wrappers. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    Wright Tract - City Properties, Los Angeles County - Picket and Kelly, Abstractors.
  - Abstract of title to the Olds Tract from the date of the preemption to January 17th 1863 made by E. V. Gillespie., 1914; 1 v. Bound in half leather. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    Olds Tract - City Properties, San Francisco County - City Abstract and Title Insurance Co.
- Research material: Land articles, rancho lists, etc.
  - Sale / development of large rancho properties. Newspaper clippings., 1912 - 1965 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    Ranchos - Publications / articles.
  - Rancho life. Clippings., 1947 - 1955 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clipping., 1950 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    Aguaje de Centinela - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Magazine clipping., 1948 Oct (Box 86, Folder 4)
    Boca de Santa Monica - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Newspaper clippings., 1957 - 1958 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    El Escorpion - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Newspaper clipping., 1962 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    La Brea - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Newspaper clippings., 1949 - 1950 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    La Puente - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Letters from Katherine B. Hotchkis., 1964 and no date; 2 items, 2 pcs. (Box 86, Folder 8)
    Los Alamitos - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Bixby, Katharine Hotchkis. Rancho Los Alamitos. Balboa, California, 1964., No dates / various dates; 2 cop. Enclosures to above. Verso title page: For W.W. Robinson, the indisputable authority on Southern California history, Katherine Bixby Hotchkis. (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Printed ephemera., 1964; Postcard, printed brochure with map, etc. (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings., 1964, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Note from Alice Titus, enclosing brochure., 1955; Los Cerritos Rancho House. (Box 86, Folder 12)
    Los Cerritos - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Newspaper clippings., 1945 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    Los Coyotes - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Newspaper clippings., 1949 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    Los Feliz - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Newspaper clipping., 1956 Apr (Box 86, Folder 15)
    Los Nietos and Santa Gertrudes Rancho Section of los Nietos - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Newspaper clipping., 1955 and no date (Box 86, Folder 16)
    Los Palos Verdes - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Newspaper clippings., 1949, no date (Box 86, Folder 17)
    Potrero de Felipe Lugo - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Romance of a rancho. In: The Beverly Hills Citizen., 1939 Bun 23; Features, v. 17 no. 2, p. [1], 6. Article is unsigned, but note gives credit to W.W. Robinson, among others. (Box 86, Folder 18)
    Rincon de los Bueyes - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - The story of El Rancho Rodeo de las Aguas. In: The Southland Federal news., 1953 Oct (Box 86, Folder 19)
    Rodeo de las Aguas - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Program for the marking of the historic Casa de Rancho San Antonio., 1946 Mar (Box 86, Folder 20)
    San Antonio - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Newspaper clipping., 1938 (Box 86, Folder 21)
    San Jose - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - [Rancho histories] In: Westwood Hills Press., 1947 Apr 17; Contains: The story of the Spanish ranchos by Florence Backus; and Westwood Hills eulogized by late poet laureate John Steven McGroaty. (Box 86, Folder 22)
    San Jose de Buenos Ayres - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Newspaper clipping., No date (Box 86, Folder 23)
    San Pedro - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Newspaper clipping., 1929 (Box 86, Folder 24)
    San Rafael - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Outlaws of Santa Susana Pass., 1953 Apr 1 (no. 4) and 1954 Oct 15 (no. 6); Mimeographed newsletters with articles on topics concerned with Rancho Simi. (Box 86, Folder 25)
    Simi - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Photograph of Camulos chapel., No dates / various dates; Removed from previous publication. (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - Casa Loma. Newspaper clipping., 1962 (Box 86, Folder 27)
    General - Ranchos, Riverside County - Publications / articles.
  - Clipping., 1949 Jan (Box 86, Folder 28)
    Santa Rosa - Ranchos, Riverside County - Publications / articles.
  - [Histories] In: The southern California rancher., 1941 - 1966; Histories of various ranches and ranchos. (Box 86, Folder 29)
    General - Ranchos, San Diego County - Publications / articles.
  - Booklist marked by WWR., No date (Box 86, Folder 30)
    San Francisco Bay Ranchos - Ranchos, San Francisco County - Publications / articles.
  - Chart of grantees, acreage, etc., No dates / various dates; 1 folded leaf. Photocopy?. (Box 86, Folder 31)
    Santa Barbara Ranchos - County Properties, Santa Barbara County - Publications / articles.
  - Rancho life and fiesta days. Newspaper clippings., 1940, 1957 (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - Newspaper clipping., 1949 (Box 86, Folder 33)
    Rosecrans Township - City Properties, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles - S.W. corner of Vermont Ave. and El Segundo Blvd
  - Clipping., 1951 Jul (Box 86, Folder 34)
    Santa Maria - City Properties, Santa Barbara County - Publications / articles.
  - Letters from the Bancroft Library concerning Mexican land grant records., 1962, 1971; 4 items, 4 pcs. (Box 87, Folder 1)
    General - Ranchos - Publications / articles.
  - Correspondence and notes., 1965; 3 items, 3 pcs. Ella Cole to WWR. Mimeographed letter from Elizabeth Carr to Ella Cole. Information about owners of the ranchos before Daniel Freeman WWR's notes. (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Letters., 1946; 2 items, 2 pcs. (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Letter to WWR from A.L. Rhodes., 1935; 1 item, 1 pc. (Box 87, Folder 4)
    Los Nietos - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - Letters from WWR to A.J. Gray., 1949 Jul; 2 items, 2 pcs. Give brief history of rancho. (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Letter to WWR from Florence ____., No date; 1 item, 1 pc. (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence., 1965 Oct, 1966 May - Bun; 4 items, 5 pcs. Also WWR's notes from envelope. Includes letter from: Don Meadows. (Box 87, Folder 7)
    General - Ranchos, Santa Barbara County - Publications / articles.
  - WWR's letters to Phil Townsend Hanna and R.W. Gray., 1949 Jul; 2 items, 2 pcs. (Box 87, Folder 8)
    San Francisco - Ranchos, Ventura County - Publications / articles.
  - Memo from W. H. Allen to WWR; concerns Redondo Villa Tract brochure., 1953; 1 item, 1 pc. Also envelope. Brochure not here. (Box 87, Folder 9)
    Redondo Villa Tract - City Properties, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - WWR's notes., No dates / various dates; 13 leaves. Holograph. 1 leaf not in WWR's hand. (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - WWR's notes., No dates / various dates; 42 leaves. Holograph. (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - WWR's notes., No dates / various dates; 1 leaf. Holograph. (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - WWR's holograph notes., No dates / various dates; 1 leaf. Holograph. (Box 87, Folder 13)
    Providencia - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Publications / articles.
  - 2/22 Patents [Report of survey of Rancho Los Palos Verdes]. Copy., 1880; 25 leaves. Typescript. (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Proceedings leading up to confirmation of Rancho Los Palos Verdes., No dates / various dates; 4 leaves. Holograph. (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - WWR's notes., No dates / various dates; 6 leaves. Holograph. (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Copies of documents., No dates / various dates; 3 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - [Rosecrans 'rancho' information]., 1949; 3 leaves. Typescript. (Box 87, Folder 18)